MANDASOIU VIOREL MARIUS



43 ani din bucuresti, necasatorit

Date contact

Email: viorelmandasoiu@yahoo.com Tel: +40732173218

Adresa:

Despre mine

8 luni

A professional hardworking and creative Head Chef with 24 years experience in catering, hotel, restaurant fine dining, cruise line ships Miami 5 star, yacht Amsterdam and hospitality industry. I am accomplished in all sections of the kitchen and work enthusiastic with a friendly approach utilizing my excellent communication skills. I am a person who is passionate about food with extensive experience of performing well under pressure in the preparation and creation of excellent food. Very sociable, I easily interact with other people and maintain a good relationship, a good knowledge of all areas in the kitchen including cost efficiency. I have good organizational skills and team work, essential to succeed in this field.

Experienta profesionala

Experienta pe	Alimentatie / HoReCa: 6 ani si 9 luni
departamente	Turism / Hotel staff: 17 ani si 4 luni

Mai 2019 - Dec 2019	Self empoyed /Sous chef -Head chef - The Fox Restaura

STRAINATATE | Turism / Hotel staff | Turism / HoReCa

Replacing the head chef or sous chef. Collaboration contract

Abilitati si competente dobandite:

Team Management

lan 2018 - Apr 2019 Self empoyed/ sous chef - Head chef - Malmaison Hotel

1 an si 4 luni STRAINATATE | Turism / Hotel staff | Turism / HoReCa

lan 2017 - Dec 2017 Head chef - Monrooe Restaurant

1 an STRAINATATE | Turism / Hotel staff | Turism / HoReCa

Salariul net: 3000 GBP

Iul 2015 - Dec 2016 Self empoyed /Head chef - Cheltenham Park Hotel

1 an si 6 luni STRAINATATE | Turism / Hotel staff | Turism / HoReCa

Salariul net: 2800 GBP

lan 2013 - Mai 2015 Self empoyed Sous chef/Head chef - Lion inn

2 ani si 5 Iuni STRAINATATE | Turism / Hotel staff | Turism / HoReCa

Salariul net: 2400 GBP

Dec 2009 - Nov 2012 Sous chef - The Market Place

3 ani STRAINATATE | Turism / Hotel staff | Turism / HoReCa

Salariul net: 2100 GBP

Mar 2007 - Dec 2009

Sous chef - Bear Hotel

2 ani si 10 luni

STRAINATATE | Turism / Hotel staff | Turism / HoReCa

Salariul net: 1800 GBP

lan 2006 - lan 2007

Sous chef - Grand Circle Amsterdam Yachting

1 an si 1 luna STRAINATATE | Turism / Hotel staff | Turism / HoReCa

Salariul net: 1700 EUR

Feb 2000 - Oct 2006

sous chef - carnival cruise lines

6 ani si 9 luni

STRAINATATE | Alimentatie / HoReCa | Turism / HoReCa

Abilitati si competente dobandite:

Communication, engleza, Team work, Punctuality, attention details

Salariul net: 1450 USD

Aug 1999 - Ian 2000

Head chef - Restaurant otopeni -Abella rocas

6 luni

Bucuresti | Turism / Hotel staff | Turism / HoReCa

Mai 1998 - Mai 1999

Senior cook - SWISSAIR

1 an si 1 luna

STRAINATATE | Turism / Hotel staff | Turism / HoReCa

Sky chef inflight catering

Mai 1996 - Apr 1998

cook - Abela rocas

2 ani

Bucuresti | Turism / Hotel staff | Turism / HoReCa

Educatie

2016 - 2016 Colegiu / Studii postliceale - Food standard agency

Food standard agency | uk

2007 - 2008 Colegiu / Studii postliceale - NCFE

NCFE LEVEL 2 CERTIFICATE IN CUSTOMER SERVICE FOR HOSPITALITY, LEISURE, TRAVEL AND TOURISM | Oxfor

2000 - 2002 Colegiu / Studii postliceale - Carnival cruise lines

limba engleza | Miami

2001 - 2001 Colegiu / Studii postliceale - Carnival cruise lines

Crowd Management Course | Miami

1997 - 1997 Colegiu / Studii postliceale - Picon sa

Limba Engleza | Bucuresti

curs incepatori ,medium, avansati

1996 - 1996 Colegiu / Studii postliceale - Hotel Turism park

Bucatar | Bucuresti

1991 - 1995 Liceu / Şcoală profesională - liceul ind electronica

Electronica | Bucuresti

Abilitati

Abilitati generale

Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel

Abilitati dobandite la locurile de munca

Communication, engleza, Team work, Punctuality, attention details, Team Management

Limbi straine

Engleză - Avansat, Spaniolă - Mediu

Alte informatii

Traininguri

FOOD ALLERGY TRAINING

perioada Feb 2016 - Feb 2016

SAFE HANDLING AND USE OF CHEMICAL CLEANING PRODUCTS

perioada Sep 2015 - Sep 2015

BACKWOOD FIRE/ FIRE AWARENESS

perioada lan 2010 - lan 2020

HACCP INFLIGHT FOOD SAFETY

perioada Mai 1999 - Mai 1999

Permis de conducere

Categoria B

dobandit in 11 oct 1997